# **PUSHPARAAJ**

Senior Creative Designer & Visual Designer

### ABOUT ME

I am Pushparaaj, specialized in Print and Digital Interface Designer. I am a very passionate designer thats always wanting to grow, learn and try something new. I love to be an anime addict this furthur led me to study Design and Visual Communication. I have years of industry experience and during my years i have worked with many companies and clients. I love what i do and do what clients love to explore.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2018-Present

2017-2018

2016-2017

2014-2016

InQ Technologies & Brahmastra

Freelance Designer

Advertising Material, Branding, Video Editing, Promotional Materials, Mobile App Design, Wireframe, Website Layout, Social Marketing

## InQ Tehnologies

Senior Creative Designer (UI/UX Designer)

UI/UX for Web and Mobile, Logo Design, Branding, Promotional Materials for Print & Web, and Design Adviser

## Opendesigns

Web Designer (Visual Designer)

Visual Designs for Web and Mobile, Logo Design, Branding, Promotional Materials for Print & Web, and Digital Illustrator

## Redox Media and Entertainment

Student and Freelancer

Learned 3DS MAX, Combustion and Smoke. Freelancer for UCMAS & Murugappa Groups

## Ad2pro Media Solutions

Junior Graphic Designer

Advertisement for Maganize & Newspaper, Real Estate Promotions, Banners, Flyers

#### SKILLS

Photoshop \_\_\_\_ Illustrator InDesign \_\_\_\_ Flash \_\_\_\_ 3ds Max Figma Adobe XD Smoke \_\_\_\_ Premiere Pro Sketch \_\_\_\_ HTML \_\_\_\_

pushparaajbalu@gmail.com

+91-9003887614

9/1, Race View Colony,

3rd Street, Guindy, Chennai-32

15-04-1993

#### LANGUAGES

#### **ACTIVITIES**

Sketching, Gaming, Researching, Story Writing, Animating & Exploring Innovative

## **EDUCATION**

2013-2015

2010-2013



# **SRM University**

BSc Visual Communication

Drawing, Visual Art, Design Principles, Advertising, Photography, Film Studies, Animation, Audiography, Soft Skills

## FIND ME ON

- in linkedin.com/in/pushparaaj-balu
- facebook.com/me.pushparaaj
  - behance.net/pushparaaj-balu